



CONTACT





gabaiz88@gmail.com





https://gabaiz88.github.io/Mi_portfolio/





LANGUAGES



- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- NODE.JS
- JAVA
- GITHUB
- SOL
- C#
- C++
- PHOTOSHOP

GABRIEL AIZMAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ANALYST **WEB DEVELOPER**

ABOUT

For the last 2 years, I have been involved in programming languages such as JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS, SASS and C#.

Prior to this, I worked in the banking and financial sector for over 14 years. These roles allowed me to develop leadership and management skills, as well as effective communication and collaboration skills. I am used to remaining calm while working in high pressure environments, and I have strong problem-solving skills.

In the last year I studied and trained in the IT area, by taking Web Development courses, as well as undertaking the Systems Analyst career in ORT Institute in Buenos Aires.

I'm looking for a new challenge that would allow me to further develop my system analyst skills.



EXPERIENCE

-BANCO CREDICOOP COOP. LTDO.

Mar 2020 - Aug 2022

Head Teller - Branch Operations Manager

-BANCO CREDICOOP COOP, LTDO.

Jun 2014 - Mar 2020

Bank Teller

-METROPOLIS CIA. FINANCIERA

Dec 2012 - Jun 2014

Credit Risk Analyst

-METROPOLIS CIA. FINANCIERA

May 2010 - Dec 2012

Head Teller



EDUCATION

-ORT INSTITUTE ARGENTINA

Aug 2021 - Present

SYSTEMS ANALYST

-CODER HOUSE

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

JAVASCRIPT

Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

WEB DEVELOPER